Hear no evil.
Speak No Evil is a horror, thriller film directed by James Watkins.
When an American family is invited to spend the weekend at the idyllic country estate of a charming British family they
befriended on vacation, what begins as a dream holiday soon warps into a snarled psychological nightmare.
Paddy, played by James McAvoy.
Louise Dalton, played by Mackenzie Davis.
Ben Dalton, played by Scoot McNairy.
Ciara, played by Aisling Franciosi.
Agnes Dalton, played by Alix West Lefler.
Ant, played by Dan Hough.
Speak No Evil is a 2024 American psychological horror thriller
film written and directed by James Watkins.
A remake of the 2022 Danish-Dutch film of the same name, the film stars James McAvoy,
Mackenzie Davis, Aisling Franciosi, Alix West Lefler, Dan Hough, and Scoot McNairy.
Its plot follows an American family who are invited to stay at a remote farmhouse of a British couple for
the weekend: the hosts soon test the limits of their guests as the situation escalates.
Jason Blum serves as a producer through his Blumhouse Productions banner.
Speak No Evil premiered at the DGA Theater in New York City on September 9, 2024, and
was released in the United States by Universal Pictures on September 13.
The film received positive reviews from critics and grossed $77
million worldwide with a budget of $15 million.
The film explores themes of husband wife relationship,
manipulation, remake, hopeless, weekend getaway.
The tone is intense and dark and mind_bending.